Nidhi kashyap

E: nidhi.bhopalkashyap@gmail.com | +91-9179223523 | A: Bhopal, Madhya Pradesh 462016

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Innovative .Net Developer with 4 years experience building and maintaining web application. Seeking the opportunities to use and enhance my skills for the Organizational goals and also enable me for more challenging and responsible jobs in IT industry.

payment. After that we create a merit list of candidate as per different department rule book.

- Technologies: ASP.NET with C#, 3 tier architecture, JavaScript, entity framework and SQL Server 2014.
- Code deployment Tool : Visual Studio 2013

WORK HISTORY

Madhya Pradesh Medical Council – **.NET Developer** MPOnline Limited Bhopal (09/2017 – Till date)

- Description: This Project is developed for Doctor's
 Provisional Registration, Permanent Registration,
 Tracking Status and to solve all queries regarding registration and Departmental approval at various levels.
- Technologies: ASP.NET with C#, 3 tier architecture, JavaScript, entity framework and SQL Server 2014.
- Code deployment Tool: Visual Studio 2013.

MPOnline Portal - .NET Developer

MPOnline Limited Bhopal (09/2017 – Till date)

- Description: This is main website of the company.
 Which include all related information through which user fill forms, get information, do payments.
- Technologies: ASP.NET with C#, 3 tier architecture, JavaScript, entity framework and SQL Server 2014.
- Code deployment Tool: Visual Studio 2013

COUNSELLING -.NET Developer

MPOnline Limited Bhopal (09/2017 – Till date)

 Description: It includes all kind of counselling like ITI Counselling, NEET UG Counselling, NEET PG Counselling, Teacher Recruitment Counselling. Project Flow is Application form, Document uploads then

SKILLS

- ASP.NET
- C#
- ADO.NET
- JavaScript
- Web Service
- Sql Server 2014

LANGUAGES

- Hindi
- English

INTERESTS

- Cooking
- Travelling
- Reading books on Self Improvement

EDUCATION

Bachelors of Engineering

Electronics & Communication Engineering 08/2013 - 07/2017 (Hons)
Oriental College of Technology, Bhopal (M.P)